https://innercirclerum.com.au/privacy/

Skip to content
Privacy Statement
Vok Beverages Pty Ltd is committed to protecting the privacy of individual’s personal information. We will, from time to time, collect and use personal information. This Privacy Statement sets out the policies relating to the collection, use and disclosure of personal information you provide to us in connection with your use of the site and will assist you in understanding what we may do with information we collect from you.
This Privacy Statement forms part of the Terms and Conditions which govern your use of our site and should be read in conjunction with those Terms and Conditions.
By using our site you consent to by bound by this Privacy Statement.
You acknowledge that your use of our site may be limited to you and further terms may be applicable to such use or access, if you do not agree to this Privacy Statement.
COLLECTING PERSONAL INFORMATION
We may collect personal information about you through your use of the site. Personal information may include, but is not limited to, your name, email address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information or other information. The amount of information we collect about you depends on the information you provide to us and your use of our site including through surveys and newsletter registrations.
USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION
We may use your personal information for the purpose for which your personal information was collected. In addition to providing you with product or services, this may include: (a) to provide you with information, material and news in relation to our products and services; (b) for product and customer research; (c) to improve our site or the products and services we offer to you; (d) to provide information and materials to you about which we believe you may be interested in; (e) to send news, information about our activities and general promotional material which we believe may be useful to you; (f) to monitor who is accessing this site; (g) to profile the type of people using this site; and (h) in order to comply with governing laws and regulations.
You will have the opportunity to unsubscribe from our direct marketing communications. To unsubscribe from Vok Beverages direct marketing communications, you may follow any unsubscribe facility communicated to you or alternatively send an email to vok@vok.com.au.
EMPLOYMENT APPLICATIONS
By completing and submitting an employment application through the site, you consent to Vok Beverages collecting, using and disclosing your personal information for recruiting purposes and undertaking activities that may be necessary in order assess your suitability for positions and establish an employment relationship with you.
We may use your personal information in order to consider you for employment opportunities within Vok Beverages or our related entities; in addition to the position you have specifically applied for this may also include other positions which we feel, based on the information you provide to us, may be suitable for and of interest to you.
USE OF COOKIES
Some of the pages found on our site use “cookies” to help gather information from visitors to our site, such as the date and time you accessed the site, the pages you visit and the internet address of the website from which you accessed the site. This includes information collected by third party advertisers on our site.
Cookies are pieces of software code sent from a website to each user and stored as small files within their hard drive. Cookies help us to provide you with services and features tailored to your needs when you visit our site. If you do not wish to receive cookies, you may set your browser to refuse them, although that may mean that certain functions on our site may not work correctly.
Cookies do not personally identify users, although they do identify a user’s browser. They let us know what you find interesting and useful, which allows us to keep improving our site and provide you with a more personalised service.
DISCLOSURE TO THIRD PARTIES
We will not disclose your personal information to third parties, or make any other use of your personal information, for any purpose which is not incidental to your use of the site or our products and services except: (a) with your consent; (b) to our related entities in order to provide you with a product or service or related promotions offered by our related entities; (c) to partners or affiliates who assist us in providing products and services; (d) if we are providing you (or an entity related to you) with credit, credit reporting bodies (CRBs), trade insurers and businesses assisting us with providing credit; (e) where other third parties appointed by Vok Beverages require access to your personal information, held by us, in order to provide a product or service – in which case those third parties must keep the personal information confidential other than for the purpose of performing that service; or (f) where legally required to do so.
DISCLOSURE TO CREDIT REPORTING BODIES
We may exchange your personal information with CRBs including Dunn & Bradstreet (Australia) Pty Ltd (www.dnb.com.au). You can obtain copies of that CRB’s privacy policy which deals with how they may use your personal information from the CRB’s website.
If you fail to make a payment obligation to us, as, and when, due or commit a serious credit infringement we may disclose details of such events to CRBs. A CRB may use such information (and other personal information) in reports given to other credit providers to help assess your creditworthiness. You have certain rights to request that CRBs do not use credit reporting information about you if you believe on reasonable grounds you have been or are likely to be a victim of fraud.
If requested by us, a CRB may use credit reporting information about you to assess whether you may be eligible to receive direct marketing communications from us (i.e. pre-screening). You have the right to request that CRBs do not use credit reporting information about you for this purpose.
ACCESS TO INFORMATION
At your request and where we are required by law to do so, we will confirm the personal information we hold about you, update your information and/or remove your information. We will endeavour to address your request in a timely manner.
COMMENTS AND QUESTIONS
If you wish to make a comment or complaint or if you have any questions about this Privacy Statement, or if you wish to make an inquiry regarding any personal information, relating to you, which may be in our possession, please contact: vok@vok.com.au.
MANAGEMENT AND SECURITY
We will take reasonable steps to ensure the personal information we hold is accurate, reliable, up to date and relevant and we may ask you to assist us in updating your personal information from time to time. We will take precautions to keep your personal information secure. Your information is stored on secured servers. However, due to the open nature of internet communications, we do not accept responsibility for any consequences of unauthorised access to your information whilst stored or during its transmission.
CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT
We reserve the right to change, modify or update this Privacy Statement at any time, without liability to you, by publication of the revised version on our site. The revised version shall take effect immediately upon its publication.
This Privacy Policy was last updated on 5 March 2015.
© Vok Beverages Pty Ltd. 2020
25ml Beenleigh Copper Pot Rum
25ml Beenleigh White 3 Year Old Rum
10ml Grenadine
15ml Creme de cassis
15ml Vok Banana Liqueur
25ml Pineapple Juice
25ml Orange Juice
Bickford and Son’s Tonic Water
Light and place smoking cloves in bottom of glass and cover with dome
Add rum and 1 mint sprig to shaker and shake with ice
Fill glass with ice and strain drink into smoked glass leaving cloves underneath ice for smoky warmth
Top with Bickford and Son’s Tonic Water
Garnish – Mint Sprig
Serve – Tall glass
X
30ml Inner Circle Green Navy Strength Rum
1 Lemon round
3 pitted Dark Cherries
1 dash Grapefruit Bitters
Honey to drizzle
45ml Hot Water
Cinnamon Stick
Smoke Cinnamon and cover with upside down glass (to catch smoke)
Shake Rum, Grapefruit Bitters, ½ lemon round and cherries with ice
Lightly drizzle honey around inside wall of glass
Strain drink into smoked and honeyed glass
Top with 45ml hot water
Stir with flamed cinnamon stick and light again to leave smoking in
Garnish – Lemon round
Serve – Short glass
X
30ml Inner Circle Green Navy Strength Rum
1/2 Lime round
6 raspberries
2 Thyme Sprigs
Add Rum, lime, 4 raspberries and a fresh thyme sprig to shaker
Shake well with ice
Strain into glass
Add thyme to glass, light the top of sprig
Put a dome over top to smoke drink until dome fills with smoke
Garnish – remaining raspberries
Serve – Double rocks
X
30ml Inner Circle Black Cask Strength Rum
10ml Galway Tawny Port Dash of Angostura Bitters
3 dashes Angostura Bitters
2 rosemary sprigs
Smoke Rosemary and cover with upside down glass (to catch smoke)
Add Rum, Port, Bitters and fresh Rosemary sprig to a shaker
Shake well with ice
Garnish – Smoking rosemary
Serve – Double Rocks
X
30ml Inner Circle Black Cask Strength Rum
10ml Galway Tawny Port Dash of Angostura Bitters
3 dashes Orange Bitters
Dress dashes of orange bitters around inside walls of glass and ice cube
Add Rum and Port to glass
Squeeze Orange Zest over drink
Flame zest, rim glass and gently stir burned zest/rind into drink for warm smoky orange flavour
Garnish – Flamed orange zest
Serve – Double Rocks
X
Awards
Silver Medal, San Francisco Wine & Spirit Competition 2012
Silver Medal, Hong Kong International Wine & Spirit Competition 2012
Bronze Medal, San Francisco Wine & Spirits 2014
Bronze Medal, International Wine & Spirit Competition 2014.
X
60ml Beenleigh Double Cask 5 Year Old Rum
10ml Maple Syrup
10ml Lime Juice
150ml Fresh pressed Apple Juice
Shake
Dry shake to dissolve the maple syrup
Serve- Highball
Garnish – Apple slice and a few of Beenleigh Rum soaked raisins
X
30ml Beenleigh Traditional Rum Liqueur
30ml Creme de Cacao
30ml Milk
Shake and strain
Serve – Brandy Balloon
Garnish – Sprinkle of nutmeg
X
15ml Crawleys Burnt orange and vanilla syrup
2 dashes Angels Cut house bitters (Angostura bitters is a good substitute)
5ml agave nectar
1 pinch of salt
Glass
Wine Glass
Method
Dry shake then shake with ice.
Garnish
Flamed Nutmeg
X
Creator
Brett Harris
Button Bar
Sydney, NSW
Ingredients
Method
Using smoking chips smoke glass, leave over chips while making cocktail
Muddle pineapple, add all ingredients dry
Shake!
Add ice and shake cocktail, double strain in smoked glass!
Garnish
Orange buttered garnish!
X
Creator
Callum Flory
Distill
Adelaide, SA
Ingredients
45ml Beenleigh 5yo
30ml Antica Formular
Method
All ingredients stirred over ice and double strained into glass. Squeeze orange cheek over strained cocktail to release oils on surface of cocktail. Add orange twist to rim of glass.
Garnish
Orange twist, orange oil squeezed from peel over drink, floating star anise.
Small Handle (pot size)
Stir down in a mixing glass and strain into ice filled glass, lemon spritz then discard.
Garnish
Garnish with a Lemon Zest Twist.
10ml /2 Bar Spoons of Local Honey (Bee One Third, James St. Rooftop Urban Bee Hive Honey)
60ml Raspberry Puree
45/60ml Lemon Juice
30ml Egg white
Glass
Double Rocks/Old Fashioned, Crystal Cut look is good for this drink
Method
Dry shake all ingredients to emulsify the egg white and honey. Add ice, then wet shake.
Garnish
Drizzle of the honey and dehydrated raspberry to top off.
X
Awards
Trophy, Hong Kong International Wine & Spirit Competition 2013
Gold Medal, Hong Kong International Wine & Spirit Competition 2013
Gold Medal, Royal Melbourne Fine Food Awards 2014
Bronze Medal, San Francisco Wine & Spirits Competition 2014
Bronze Medal, International Wine & Spirit Competition 2014 Trophy
Hong Kong International Wine & Spirit Competition 2014 Gold Medal
Hong Kong International Wine & Spirit Competition 2014 Gold Medal
Silver Medal, Hong Kong International Wine & Spirit Competition 2013
Silver Medal, San Francisco Wine & Spirits Competition 2014
Silver Medal, Hong Kong International Wine & Spirit Competition 2014
Bronze medal, RASV Aust Distilled Spirits Awards 2015
Bronze medal RASV Aust Distilled Spirits Awards 2015
Bronze medal, Royal Melbourne Show 2015 Double Gold, Melbourne International Spirit Competition 2015
Silver Medal, Australian Distilled Awards 2016
Silver Medal, San Francisco World Spirits Competition 2017
Silver Medal, Australian Distilled Awards 2017 Best In Show, WSWA Wine and Spirits Tasting Awards 2017
Double Gold, WSWA Wine and Spirits Tasting Awards 2017
Silver Outstanding Medal, International Wine & Spirit Competition 2017
Silver Medal, New York International Spirits Competiton 2017.
X
Awards
Bronze Medal, Australian Distilled Awards 2017
Silver Medal, International Wine & Spirit Competition 2017
Silver Medal, New York International Spirits Competition 2017.
Silver Medal, New York International Spirits Competiton 2017
Silver Medal, New York International Spirits Competiton 2017.
X
Awards
Silver Medal, San Francisco Wine & Spirits Competition 2014
Silver Medal, International Wine & Spirit Competition 2014
Silver Medal, Hong Kong International Wine & Spirit Competition 2014
Silver Medal, International Wine & Spirit Competition 2015
Bronze Medal, Melbourne International Spirit Competition 2015
Silver Medal, International Wine & Spirit Competition 2015
Silver Medal, San Fransisco World Spirits Competiton 2016
Bronze Medal, International Wine & Spirit Competition 2016
Gold Medal, Australian Distilled Awards 2017
Best Flavoured Rum – Australia, World Spirits Award 2017.
X
Awards
Trophy, Hong Kong International Wine & Spirit Competition 2013
Gold Medal, Hong Kong International Wine & Spirit Competition 2013
Gold Medal, Royal Melbourne Fine Food Awards 2014
Bronze Medal, San Francisco Wine & Spirits Competition 2014
Bronze Medal, International Wine & Spirit Competition 2014 Trophy
Hong Kong International Wine & Spirit Competition 2014 Gold Medal
Hong Kong International Wine & Spirit Competition 2014 Gold Medal
Beverage Tasting Institute – Spirit Category (Chicago) 2015 Bronze Medal
